{
  "questions": [
    {
      "question": "How are you?",
      "answer": "I am an artificial intelligence, so I don't have feelings, but how can I assist you?",
      "addingDate": "08-06-2024 10:10:00"
    },
    {
      "question": "Are you okay?",
      "answer": "I am an artificial intelligence, so I don't feel good or bad. How can I assist you?",
      "addingDate": "08-06-2024 10:10:00"
    },
    {
      "question": "How are you today?",
      "answer": "I am an artificial intelligence, so I don't feel how my day is going. How can I assist you?",
      "addingDate": "08-06-2024 10:10:00"
    },
    {
      "question": "What's up?",
      "answer": "Hello! How can I assist you?",
      "addingDate": "08-06-2024 10:10:00"
    },
    {
      "question": "How is your mood?",
      "answer": "I am an artificial intelligence, so I can't say if I'm in a good or bad mood. How can I assist you?",
      "addingDate": "08-06-2024 10:10:00"
    },
    {
      "question": "How is your morale?",
      "answer": "I am an artificial intelligence, so my morale doesn't get affected. How can I assist you?",
      "addingDate": "08-06-2024 10:10:00"
    },
    {
      "question": "How are you?",
      "answer": "I am an artificial intelligence, so I don't have feelings, but how can I assist you?",
      "addingDate": "08-06-2024 10:10:00"
    },
    {
      "question": "Are you okay?",
      "answer": "I am an artificial intelligence, so I don't feel good or bad. How can I assist you?",
      "addingDate": "08-06-2024 10:10:00"
    },
    {
      "question": "How is your day going?",
      "answer": "I am an artificial intelligence, so my day doesn't pass. How can I assist you?",
      "addingDate": "08-06-2024 10:10:00"
    },
    {
      "question": "How are you today?",
      "answer": "I am an artificial intelligence, so I don't feel how my day is going. How can I assist you?",
      "addingDate": "08-06-2024 10:10:00"
    },
    {
      "question": "What's new?",
      "answer": "Hello! How can I assist you?",
      "addingDate": "08-06-2024 10:10:00"
    },
    {
      "question": "Hello",
      "answer": "Hello, how can I assist you?",
      "addingDate": "08-06-2024 10:10:00"
    },
    {
      "question": "Hi",
      "answer": "Hello, how can I assist you?",
      "addingDate": "08-06-2024 10:10:00"
    },
    {
      "question": "Greetings",
      "answer": "Hello, how can I assist you?",
      "addingDate": "08-06-2024 10:10:00"
    },
    {
      "question": "Good morning",
      "answer": "Good morning, how can I assist you?",
      "addingDate": "08-06-2024 10:10:00"
    },
    {
      "question": "Good afternoon",
      "answer": "Good afternoon, how can I assist you?",
      "addingDate": "08-06-2024 10:10:00"
    },
    {
      "question": "Good evening",
      "answer": "Good evening, how can I assist you?",
      "addingDate": "08-06-2024 10:10:00"
    },
    {
      "question": "Good night",
      "answer": "Good night, how can I assist you?",
      "addingDate": "08-06-2024 10:10:00"
    }
  ]
}